<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ListView</string>
    <string name="Android"> Android is a mobile operating system developed
        by Google, based on the Linux kernel and designed primarily
        for touchscreen mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets.
        for cars, and Android Wear for wrist watches, each with a specialized user interface.
        Variants of Android are also used on game consoles, digital cameras, PCs and other electronics.

    Android is a mobile operating system developed
        by Google, based on the Linux kernel and designed primarily
        for touchscreen mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets.
        for cars, and Android Wear for wrist watches, each with a specialized user interface.
        Variants of Android are also used on game consoles, digital cameras, PCs and other electronics.

    </string>
    <string name="iOS">
        "iOS is Apple's mobile operating system used to run the popular iPhone, iPad,
        and iPod Touch devices. Formerly known as the iPhone OS, the name was changed
        with the introduction of the iPad iOS utilizes a multi-touch interface where simple
        gestures are used to operate the device, like swiping your
    </string>
<string name="BlackBerry">
    BlackBerry is a leading cybersecurity software and services company dedicated to securing the Enterprise of Things
                        Based in Waterloo, Ontario, the company was founded in 1984 and operates in North America, Europe,
                        Asia, Australia, Middle East, Latin America and Africa.
</string>
    <string name="Rimos">
        Significado de Rimos\nRimos vem do verbo rir. O mesmo que: chalaceamos, chocarreamos, gargalhamos, gracejamos, sorrimos.
    </string>
    <string name="Symbian">
        In 2009, we established the Symbian Foundation to make the Symbian platform available open source and royalty-free. In November 2010 we announced that the foundation
        would ramp down its operational activities as a result of changes in global economic and market conditions.
        We have now completed the transition from a non-profit organisation responsible for governing the open
    </string>

    <string name="Webos">
        WebOS is an LG-owned, Linux-based, smart TV operating system that is set up to allow control and access
        of LG Smart TV’s more advanced features and connected devices through a graphical user interface (GUI).
        WebOS was developed  by Palm as a mobile OS. The company released it  in 2009 as Palm webOS. Hewlett Packard
        acquired palm in April 2010. The operating system was used in a number of Palm and HP smartphones.
    </string>



</resources>
